GitHub: https://github.com/

Dee 1985

Portfolio: https://

dee1985.github.io/basic-portfolio/

AYDY BURLING

Résumé of Qualifications

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aydy-burling

Email: aydy.you@gmail.com

Mobile: 651-334-8822

Professional Full Stack Developer and Health Care Leader

Certified professional full stack developer with more than 10+ years as a nursing leader making a career transition from health care to web development and seeking to apply strengths and experience to new settings.

- Motivated and knowledgeable with a proven record of academic achievement and career development.
- Successful in managing multiple tasks and meeting team and individual goals in an everchanging environment.
- Strong organizational and project management skills to identify problems and develop solutions based on customers' needs.
- Adept at working with diverse groups around mutual goals and collaborating as a team member.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL
- Frameworks & Libraries: ReactJS, Node, Express, Bootstrap, Material UI
- Continuing Education: Java, Spring, Linux, Python, Angular
- Other: Epic EMR, PowerPoint, Word, Excel

DEV PROJECTS

Brew Cruz: https://github.com/Dee1985/project-one

Live Site: https://dee1985.github.io/project-one/

An application to locate breweries while traveling. Utilizes JS, open source APIs for breweries and MapQuest, Bulma.

Which Witch: https://github.com/Dee1985/which-witch

Live Site: https://dee1985.github.io/which-witch/

A simple word guessing game. Utilizes JS, Bootstrap, HowlerJS

Shopping List: https://github.com/Dee1985/React-Shopping-List

Live Site: https://aydy-react-shopping-list.netlify.com/

A simple list app- add, delete and save items. Saves to local storage. Utilizes ReactJS.

EXPERIENCE

MINNESOTA DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, Saint Paul, MN

Nurse Supervisor/Team Lead, COVID-19 Response, Aug. 2020 – Dec. 2020

- Contributing to the development of the COVID-19 Response. Continuously
 assisting the Healthcare leadership team to develop and implement creative
 solutions to issues impacting Long Term Care Facilities in MN, specifically for
 the COVID Case Manager (CCM) team.
- Creating and managing workflow for COVID case managers. Creating tools to streamline processes and increase individual and team engagement, moral, and productivity.
- Identify training and education needs, step changes for process improvement, developing, implementing, and improving onboarding and orientation process
- Managing team schedules, timesheets and addressing personal related issues or concern

GitHub: https://github.com/

Dee 1985

Portfolio: https://dee1985.github.io/

basic-portfolio/

AYDY BURLING

Résumé of Qualifications

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/aydy-burling

Email: aydy.you@gmail.com Mobile: 651-334-8822

HENNEPIN COUNTY MEDICAL CENTER, Minneapolis, MN

Registered Nurse, Surgical/Trauma Neuroscience ICU, Aug. 2016 to Nov. 2019

- Continually working within the context of the Hennepin Health "Centered Around You" Patient and Family Centered Care practice model to provide and coordinate nursing care by protecting, promoting, and optimizing health.
- Preventing illness and injury and alleviating suffering through the nursing diagnosis and treatment of the human response; partnering with the patient, their family and significant others.

Registered Nurse/Charge nurse, Medical/Surgical Inpatient, Oct. 2010 to Aug. 2016

- Continually working within the context of the Hennepin County Medical Center "Centered Around You" Patient and Family Centered Care practice model to provide and coordinate nursing care by protecting, promoting and optimizing health
- Creating staff schedules and managing bed assignments per unit and hospital policy.

Registered Nurse/Triage, Acute Psychiatric Services, Oct. 2010 to Aug. 2016

- Identifying and prioritizing critical care cases in an emergency department setting
 for admission, transfer or discharge. Triaging new and return adult and child/
 adolescent patients regarding their mental health needs, questions and/or
 concerns.
- Management of the Suicide prevention and crisis line. Providing clients and their families' resource information regarding any mental health emergency. Crisis interventions completed, as necessary.

Registered Nurse, *Inpatient Psychiatry*, Oct. 2009 to Aug. 2016

- Defining and identifying common psychiatric disorders.
- Identifying and utilizing medications and other approved therapies for psychiatric disorders.
- Knowledge of behavioral assessment, use of therapeutic response and other treatment techniques.

HIGHLIGHTS

Certified in Full stack web development

Selected as Team Lead for MN COVID-19 response pilot program in 2020

Selected as Co-chair for the development and execution of the 18th Annual Trauma Life in the ICU national conference in 2019

Selected as an HCMC Nurse Scholar in 2013- enhanced patient centered care with Evidenced Based Research

Basic Life Support, Advanced Cardiac Life Support, Public Health Nurse

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Certification, 2020, University of Minnesota, Saint Paul, MN

Bachelor's Degree in Nursing, 2009, Saint Catherine University, Saint Paul, MN

REFERENCES

Available upon request